Dwivedianurag483@gmail.com

#### I Myself

Hi, My name is Anurag Dubey, and I have 7 years of experience developing full-stack applications to scale and integrate distributed systems. I have completed my Bachelor Of Computer Application from Punjab Technical University.

I want many hats as a full-stack developer and have not limited myself to just one stack. On backend programming, I use PHP and on the frontend spectrum, I enjoy coding in React ,GraphQL HTML, CSS, javascript, and frameworks like VueJs. I have also designed large datasets on MySQL.

I have excellent exposure to REST API design into security. So I know my way around SSL, cookies, tokens, and so on. All my projects were based on TDD (Test Driven Development). Focusing on and resolving application defects, Testing, debugging, and refining the software as a whole.

At this stage of my career, I am still very keen and learning new technologies. I want to work for a company which will not only challenge my technical expertise but would also provide me with attractive career opportunities.

Thank you for your time. If you want to reach me, you can find the details in my profile.

#### Career Objective

I am hard working and able to prioritise a huge volume of work. I believe that a diplomatic approach to problem-solving is also very important. I am also able to work well on my own initiative and can demonstrate the high levels of motivation required to meet the tightest of deadlines. Even under significant pressure, I possess a strong ability to perform effectively.

#### Secondary & Higher Secondary School

Course (Stream)/Examination	Institution/University	Month/ Year of Passing	Performance
High School	S.A. Inter College(UP Board)	2009	52.5%
Intermediate	R.B.S.S Inter College(UP Board)	2011	47.2%

#### **Bachelor Education**

#### BCA Bachelor Of Computer Application (Punjab Technical University)

Year	Total Marks	Obtained Marks	Percentage
Ist Year	1450	1113	76.75%
IInd Year	1400	1078	77.00%
IIIrd Year	1400	1123	80.21%

#### My Global Presence

<u>LinkedIn</u> (https://www.linkedin.com/in/anurag-dubey-05203017a/)

- <u>GitHub</u> (https://github.com/anuragamit)
- Facebook (www.facebook.com/anurag.dubey.90226)

## My Skills & Technical Expertise

#### **Core Skills**

Software developments

# Programming Skills

- JavaScript (ECMAScript)
- React JS
- GraphQL
- PHP (laravel Core & OOP)
- HTML5
- CSS3

### JavaScript Frameworks & Libraries

- JQuery
- Bootstrap
- VueJs
- Next JS

### PHP CMS & Frameworks

- Laravel
- Codeignaiter
- Wordpress (Divi,Visual Composer, Mentor)
- Woocommerce
- Opencart
- MVC & MVCL Based Own Framework

### **Experience With Web Servers**

- Apache 2
- Nginx

# Experience With DB Servers

MySql

### **Application Programming Interface (API)**

- Stripe Payment API
- Klarna Payment API
- Ebay API
- Gunbroker API
- Pusher Messaging Notification API
- Paypal Payment API

### Build Tools & Package Manager

- Webpacks
- Babel (JavaScript transpiler)
- NPM
- Composer

### Git Hosting Platforms (CVS)

- Bitbucket
- Gitlab
- GitHub

### Developer Tools (IDE)

- Netbeans 8.2 (FTP/SFTP)
- Git
- Filezilla
- Putty SSH Client
- Draw.io
- Postman
- VSCode

# **Experience in Domains (Work Based on IT Services)**

- Real Estate
- Medical
- Hospitality
- Multi-level Marketing (MLM)
- e-Commerce
- Education sector

### **Work Experiences**

Full Stack Developer, 06/2023 to current

**JMD WEB. -** Netherland

**Full Stack Developer,** 11/2022 to 06/2023

Mediscribes Solutions India private Limited. - Ahmedabad Gujarat 380006

Full Stack Developer, 11/2021 to 2022 Tech Media Search Pvt Ltd. - Noida UP

Full Stack Developer, 11/2019 to 2021

OSculus Communication LLP. - Noida UP

- Developed an automation tool for rebate and keyword tracking.
- Developing conversational AI and Brand analytics for e-commerce.
- Contributed ideas and suggestions in team meetings and delivered updates on deadlines, designs and enhancements.

**Sr Web Developer,** 08/2018 to 09/2019

Lat2 Inteligencia pvt. Itd - Jankipuram Lucknow, Uttar Pradesh

- Designed, developed and implemented software applications for websites based on analysed requirements and understanding of industry technical standards.
- Planned and engineered RESTful web services to manipulate dynamic datasets.
- Developed functional digital design concepts across various platforms to strengthen company brand and identity.

Web Developer, 09/2017 to 07/2018

Virtuoso IT Solution - Lucknow, Uttar Pradesh

- Assisted web presence planning, implementing changes and integrating requested elements to streamline business operations.
- Researched new technologies, software packages and hardware products for use in website projects.
- Developed wireframes, site maps and content inventories for new website designs.security and efficiency.

#### My Recent Projects

- ADMINISTRATIEIGENCHAUFFEUR.NL(CRM)
- <u>BIMIBOOKS.NL</u>(MAGAZINE)
- <u>ZOOPUP.COM</u> (Freelancer Software)

- <u>BIGGERBIDS.COM</u>(Ecommerce Product Selling)
- <u>HEALTHASHTAM.COM</u> (Ecommerce & MLM)
- <u>COMPETENSEA.COM</u> (Maritime Industry )
- AXISENGLISH.CO.UK (Blog)
- ORDERHUBPLUS.COM (Product Order)
- <u>DREAM11CRICKETTEAM.COM</u>(Blog News)
- <u>WELCOMEINDIAEDU.COM</u> (Animation)
- <u>BEONE.COM.SA</u> (Logistic Software)
- <u>DEALSINFO.IN</u> (Advertisement)
- <u>WWW.STARFUTUREGROUP.COM</u> (Real Estate)
- <u>WWW.HYPERLAND.COM</u> (Real Estate)
- <u>WWW.SHBIGSTAR.COM</u> (Basic Website + MLM Software)
- <u>WWW.MATRIMONYLIFE.COM</u> (Marriage Software)
- <u>WWW.GETTEACHERS.COM</u> (Tution Tutor)
- <u>WWW.POGIMPEX.COM</u> (Website)
- <u>AYNMA.COM</u>(Ecommerce)
- RJINFRACITY.COM